Sourabh Kumar Goyal



34 Luv Kush Nagar, Mansarovar, Jaipur, Rajasthan, 302020

+917727996709

Sourabhkumar20031995@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/sourabh -kumar-goyal-38410a1a1/

Summary

Started journey with one of the top MNCs Infosys, one year was very productive, switched to a small company to explore and learn new skills. Ecommerce, Client Management, Finance and Accounting Social Media handler, Digital Marketing, People Management, an aspiring life coach.

Highlights

- Ecommerce seller central and Online Marketing
- Social Media Handler
- Procure to Pay
- An Aspiring Life Coach and Psychologist
- Swimming and Dancing

Experience

ACCOUNTANT – 12/16 to 12/2017 **INFOSYS,** JAIPUR

- Procure to Pay, Accounts Payable
- SAP, Author Set Up, AS-400, Royalty Payment
- Contract Setup, Worked on Six Sigma
- Part of Quality team

Ecommerce Manager - 01/2018 to 01/2022 **Amazing Gems & Jewelers**, Jaipur

- Procure to Pay, Raising Demand to Final Payment
- Handling Alibaba, eBay, ETSY, Amazon
- Hiring new talents in company
- Social Media Marketing, email Marketing
- Client and People Management

Provisioning Analyst – 01/2022 to Present **London Stock Exchange,** Bangalore

Vendor Management

Onboarding, Offboarding, SAP(Fieldglass), Data Management, Manager Mapping, Validation

Education

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE, 2016 MASTERS IN ACCOUNTING, 2018 MASTERS IN PSYCHOLOGY, 2021 TO NOW NLP, NEURO LINGUSTIC PROGRAMMING

ACHIVEMENTS

- Second Rank in district Core Academy Exam
- Gold Medalist in Avantika Essay Writing Competition
- Scouts Member
- Spot Award for outstanding work in Infosys
- Part of eBay community member